window.canvas ={};
window.canvas.data = [{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Advertising scope and content","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.82,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Atmosphere in compartment (friendly\\not friendly)","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.83},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Availability of information about behavior in contingency situations","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.74,"change_response":0.83},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Availability of information about behavior in contingency situations","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.53,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Available information to select an optimal ticket","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.38},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Behavior of fare collectors","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.72,"change_response":0.65},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Behavior of fare collectors","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.37,"change_response":0.83},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Car free space","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.84},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Cleanliness at stations","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.83,"change_response":0.74},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Cleanliness in compartment","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Cleanliness in compartment","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.48,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Comfort and length of route during transfer","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.64,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Comfort of seats","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.45,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Comfort when boarding","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.25},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Compartment atmosphere","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.35,"change_response":0.72},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Compartment climate","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.73,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Compartment free space","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.73,"change_response":0.46},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Condition and convenience of motor vehicles","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.84},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Condition of stops","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.32,"change_response":0.37},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Condition of trains and tunnels","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.54,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Convenience of boarding\\alighting","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.98},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Convenience of route planning at the stop","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.25},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Distance to station","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.54,"change_response":0.52},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Distance to stop","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.63,"change_response":0.34},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Escalator boarding speed","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.37,"change_response":0.83},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Length and comfort of travel during transfer","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.53,"change_response":0.38},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Length of transfer between stations","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.45,"change_response":0.53},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Metro","question":"Metro transportation satisfaction","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.8,"change_response":0.36},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Mobile and Internet communication quality","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.74},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"NGPT","question":"NGPT transportation satisfaction","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.85,"change_response":0},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Navigation convenience during travel","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.83},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Navigation convenience upon transfer","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.47,"change_response":0.84},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Navigation during travel","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.64,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Navigation when exiting from station","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.74,"change_response":0.25},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Noise level","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.35},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.15,"change_response":0},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.32,"change_response":0},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.76,"change_response":0},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.81,"change_response":0},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.54,"change_response":0},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.63,"change_response":0},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.65,"change_response":0},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.73,"change_response":0},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.56,"change_response":0},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.53,"change_response":0},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.25,"change_response":0},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Overall","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.56,"change_response":0},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Pace of ticket purchase in ticket office","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.23,"change_response":0.23},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Pace of ticket purchase in ticket offices and ticket vending machines","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.63,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Pace of ticket purchase in ticket offices and ticket vending machines change","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.63,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Protection against weather conditions on stops","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.37},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Safety in terms of administrative offences","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.54,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Safety in terms of administrative offences at stops","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.53,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Safety in terms of administrative offences in transport","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.64,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Safety in terms of transport when waiting at the stop","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.53,"change_response":0.93},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Safety of standing at platform","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.34,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Ticket purchase and waiting comfort","question":"Sanitary condition of entrance","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.65,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Subway car climate","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.37,"change_response":0.93},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Train travel smoothness","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.93,"change_response":0.84},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Transport accessibility early morning and late at night","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.64,"change_response":0.83},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Transport accessibility early morning and late at night change","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.6,"change_response":0.64},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Transport boarding time","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.83,"change_response":0.28},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Transport boarding time change","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Travel speed predictability","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.46,"change_response":0.63},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Traveling comfort to/from station","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.74,"change_response":0.35},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Transport accessibility","question":"Traveling comfort to/from stop","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.53,"change_response":0.84},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Traveling interval","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.23,"change_response":0.83},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Traveling interval change","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.73},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Safety","question":"Traveling safety and smoothness","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.74,"change_response":0.45},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Traveling speed","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.23,"change_response":0.43},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Traveling speed change","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":0,"response":0.64,"change_response":0.62},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Trip planning tools","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":4,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.84},{"type":"Metro","quality_aspect":"Planning and navigation opportunities","question":"Trip planning tools","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":3,"response":0.74,"change_response":0.35},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Visibility of windows (clean not pasted with advertising)","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.27},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Waiting and trip time predictability","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":2,"response":0.32,"change_response":0.52},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Speed and predictability","question":"Waiting and trip time predictability change","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.36,"change_response":0.83},{"type":"NGPT","quality_aspect":"Comfort en route","question":"Wi-Fi connection quality","survey_year":2014,"survey_quarter":1,"importance":1,"response":0.45,"change_response":0.83}]